esearchvision.com 2016-12-08

# Privacy Agency | ESV Digital

## **Privacy** Policy

## **Terms of use and privacy policy (last updated November 15th, 2012)**

ESV Digital SA, together with its existing or future subsidiaries ( collectively “ESV Digital”, “us”, or “our”), is a digital marketing company that provides hosted software platforms and consulting and account management services to customers (“customers”) for search marketing, social media advertising, mobile marketing, online display and video marketing as well as tracking of online marketing campaigns. We also make available our corporate website at the following URL address: www.esvdigital.com.

ESV Digital provides these terms of use and privacy policy to inform you of our policies and procedures related to the collection, use and disclosure of information we receive in connection with your visit to this website or the use of our software platform and services by our clients.

## **1\. Corporate Website**

We may collect personal information on our visitors through an analysis of the logs of our webpage server as well as through the potential use of cookies and/or web analytics software. This information may include your IP (Internet Protocol) address. The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. Visiting ESV Digital’s website with your browser settings adjusted to accept cookies tells us that you want to use ESV Digital’s products and services and that you consent to our use of cookies and other technologies to provide them to you as described in this notice. We also collect personal information through the “contact us” online form available on our website. This information may include but not be limited to first name, surname, address, company, position, online marketing budgets as well as e-mail and telephone number. This information will not be transferred to third parties and will be used for the sole purpose of developing our business or answering your specific query. We may archive those personal and non-personal data for as long as we think they can be of any use to us or archive them for longer periods of time.

## **2\. Our hosted software platform**

As part of the services we provide to our clients, we track through our platform as well as on our clients’ website end users’ interactions with customer advertisements and customer sites, such as clicks on advertisements, impressions and conversions, whether on a single customer site or across multiple sites, but all on an anonymous basis. As part of this tracking process on our platform, we do not collect any personally identifiable information but we may collect IP addresses. Again, we will never seek to identify you personally through your IP address unless so requested by governmental or other judicial authorities.

Our tracking technology may employ tracking pixels on customer sites as well as data feeds from our customers or from third parties. A tracking pixel is a piece of code embedded on a web page of customer sites that collects information about visitors’ behavior on that web page. The tracking pixel can either be provided by the customer, by ESV Digital or by some of our technical partners. The tracking pixel may include a command to create cookies. A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on a user’s browser and that enables tracking activity from a browser. The typical lifetime of the cookies we create is one year, although this duration may be changed at any time and without advance notice to our customers and end users. Any end user may elect to opt out from enabling cookies in his browser’s settings tools by choosing between several options offered by the browser.

Any customer-specific data we collect are the property of our customers and will be transferred to them upon request. We do not guarantee the privacy policy or data treatment of our customers with respect to the data we transfer to them.

Within ESV Digital, those data will be used for the sole purpose of feeding our algorithms and other analytical steps with the aim of improving the marketing performance of our customers. We do not share, distribute, sell or rent any of the collected information in our possession with third parties, except where requested by our customers. However, we may share information if so requested by governmental or other judicial authorities.

As part of the Services we provide, the only personal information we gather are various contact information for our customers. We may archive those data for as long as we think they can be of any use, but will typically delete them when we no longer provide our Services to a customers. We may also elect to archive them for longer periods of time.

## **3\. Terms applying to both our corporate website and our hosted software platform**

This corporate website and our hosted software platform are edited by ESV Digital SA, 18 rue de Londres, 75009 Paris, France, a corporation organized under the laws of France and its director of publication is Stanislas di Vittorio. They are hosted by Colt technology Services, 23-27 rue Pierre Valette, 92247 Malakoff Cedex, France, and any dispute arising hereunder will be subject to the laws of France and the courts of Paris, France.

You may access, modify and delete any personal information by contacting us at contact@ESV Digital.com or by writing to us at ESV Digital SA, 18 rue de Londres, 75009 Paris, France. We have reasonable security measures in place to help protect both personal and non-personal information that we collect, included back-up systems, firewalls and login/password and encryption of the access to our hosted software platform. However, no system can be completely secure, and we make no guarantees as to the safety or security of any information transmitted through our Services.

All information collected hereunder is stored in a hosting center located in the European Union and we abide by the European Commission’s Directive on Data Protection of October 1998. ESV Digital reserves the right to modify this policy at any time and without prior notice. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the revised privacy policy via our corporate website (this website). You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes.

To address any questions, comments, or concerns related to our privacy policy, please contact us at contact@esvdigital.com or by mail at ESV Digital, 18 rue de Londres, 75009 Paris, France.

**Tell our customers not to measure your use of their websites :[click here](https://tracking.esearchvision.com/optout/optout_en.html).**
